now it's important to find the right mix
of old and new
so the solar panels
good morning
okay guys so this is going to be our
biggest project for this film this year
and since most of the work is going to
happen off-site
we cannot take any chances now i know
that sunidhi specializes in heritage
architecture that's why i've decided
that
sunni
is going to assist anand full time on
this project
anand will handle it
anan you leave the renovation so but i
can take those remember guys it's a team
effort
okay
so the whole idea is to reinvent the
entire thing keeping the foundation
intact any thoughts suggestions
so
now that we have a chance to reinvent
why don't we start with breaking that
ceiling
what ceiling that's a courtyard where's
the ceiling
yes sir that
invisible glass ceiling
[Music]
barriers faced by women in the workplace
may not be apparent at first
this women's day green lamb urges you to
give the glass ceiling another look
[Music]